Guide to the Richard Foreman and Kate Manheim Papers MSS.152
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIV: Media
  - Subseries B: Sound Effects - Originals
    - Title: Piano Spastic (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0129)
    - Title: Toll (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0130)
    - Title: Crackle (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0131)
      Tape Brand: BASF Ferro Super LH I
    - Title: Horn Ompf (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0132)
    - Title: ChooCho (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0133)
    - Title: 112 Cantor / 115 Act 7 (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0134)
    - Title: Drum Heart (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0135)
    - Title: Heroic (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0136)
      Tape Brand: Sony HF 46 Type I (Normal)
    - Title: Piano (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0137)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I (Normal) Position EF
    - Title: Tone 1 (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0138)
      Tape Brand: Maxell Position Normal UR
    - Title: Clicks (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0139)
    - Title: Ring-it (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0140)
    - Title: P. Folk (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0141)
    - Title: Firemusic (M) (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0142)
    - Title: Indra Twitch (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0143)
    - Title: Totle Mesan (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0144)
    - Title: Arab Slo (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0145)
    - Title: H. Frantic, cuid34709 (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0146)
      Duration: 32 minutes
    - Title: Horn (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0147)
    - Title: Yowl / Coolhip (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0148)
    - Title: Base Echo (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0149)
    - Title: Drum Wobble (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0150)
      Tape Brand: TDK D-C60
    - Title: Fandango (M) (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0151)
    - Title: Harpsi Jap (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0152)
    - Title: Prance (Box 1B.a, Folder ID: 152.0153)
    - Title: Bells (B: Omph / giggle) (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0154)
      Tape Brand: TDK
    - Title: Violin Heart Wistful (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0155)
    - Title: E ditto (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0156)
    - Title: Scream / Slo Disco Pluck (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0157)
    - Title: P Role (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0158)
    - Title: Ask / Sadly (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0159)
    - Title: Orc Lo (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0160)
    - Title: Eng / Tico Filter (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0161)
    - Title: Industry Long (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0162)
    - Title: Single Bee (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0163)
    - Title: G Chug / Honk (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0164)
    - Title: Roses (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0165)
      Tape Brand: MA-XG Metal Position Type IV
    - Title: Bambo / ladies (Box 1C, Folder ID: 153.0166)
    - Title: Soprano (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0167)
    - Title: Chug / Columbus (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0168)
    - Title: Trill / Org Slo (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0169)
    - Title: G. Fling (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0170)
    - Title: Drum (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0171)
    - Title: Violin Round (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0172)
    - Title: Bop / Soft X (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0173)
    - Title: Triste (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0174)
      Tape Brand: Memorex MRX I
    - Title: Good BT / Jungle (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0175)
      Tape Brand: Maxell XL II Position High 60
    - Title: Last Voice (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0176)
    - Title: Organ Klee (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0177)
    - Title: Turndot Cord 2 (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0178)
    - Title: Chug / Columbus (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0179)
      Tape Brand: TDK IEC II / Type II High Position SA
      Tape Length: 76
    - Title: Sop Rnd / Bach Jz (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0180)
      Tape Brand: TDK IEC I / Type I Normal Position
    - Title: Faure / Chinese (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0181)
    - Title: Strum (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0182)
    - Title: Pluck / Samba (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0183)
      Tape Brand: Philips Chromium
    - Title: Lalo: Lament (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0184)
    - Title: BT Rat tat (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0185)
      Tape Brand: Memorex dB Series
    - Title: Cramp 2 / Pump (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0186)
    - Title: Waltz (L) (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0187)
    - Title: Bali (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0188)
    - Title: Hesitation (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0189)
    - Title: Hoc down long (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0190)
    - Title: Sop insist (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0191)
    - Title: Tung / Mellow (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0192)
    - Title: Who do / org scale (B: Bach 4) (Box 1C, Folder ID: 152.0193)
    - Title: Child Choral / Train Blare (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0194)
    - Title: Kazoo (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0195)
    - Title: Yid - Clarnet Twang (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0196)
    - Title: Fst. Flute / Flr. Drum (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0197)
    - Title: Lost (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0198)
    - Title: Rnski (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0199)
    - Title: Claranet / Tap 2 (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0200)
    - Title: Lite chug (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0201)
    - Title: Wist old (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0202)
    - Title: Cool T (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0203)
    - Title: Airplane / Weil (A: Babes 1) (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0204)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I (Normal) Position AHF
    - Title: Cheeps (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0205)
    - Title: Wood Xylo B / Sop Insist (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0206)
    - Title: Gentle (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0207)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I (Normal) HF
    - Title: Trumpt / P juste (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0208)
    - Title: Toll - St (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0209)
    - Title: Organ Rich (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0210)
    - Title: M. Idle / Sop (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0211)
    - Title: Drum 2 (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0212)
      Tape Brand: TDK Type II High Position SA-X90
    - Title: Piano Vamp (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0213)
    - Title: Pots n Pans / Dan 18 (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0214)
    - Title: Atmos. (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0215)
    - Title: Slow March (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0216)
      Tape Brand: Esic Hi-Fi Low-Noise
    - Title: Lyric (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0217)
    - Title: Sop High (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0218)
    - Title: Rumba (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0219)
    - Title: D-H Squek (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0220)
    - Title: Swing (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0221)
    - Title: Lament (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0222)
    - Title: Chant (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0223)
    - Title: III Bears (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0224)
      Tape Brand: Drummond Classic
    - Title: Hoots (Swings) (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0225)
    - Title: Tom Tom 2 (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0226)
    - Title: Soph / Alpha (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0227)
    - Title: Drum Rhym (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0228)
    - Title: Door 2 (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0229)
    - Title: E Pling (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0230)
    - Title: P Bang (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0231)
    - Title: Tabula (Box 1C.a, Folder ID: 152.0232)
    - Title: ORG Start / Mex Squeze (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0233)
    - Title: Acc Chug / P. Vamp (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0234)
    - Title: Clock #16 / Johnson (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0235)
      Tape Brand: Maxell XL II
    - Title: Vamp / Alp (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0236)
    - Title: #75 Boris Melo (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0237)
      Tape Brand: Scotch 3M
    - Title: Party Slo (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0238)
    - Title: Eliot Sharp (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0239)
    - Title: Dra (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0240)
    - Title: Flute BT / Sway (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0241)
    - Title: Popsi / Visslar For Loop (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0242)
    - Title: girlfriend / 2 chord (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0243)
    - Title: Orch. Scale (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0244)
    - Title: Magic / Sop L (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0245)
    - Title: Crow (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0246)
    - Title: Rumple / Prance (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0247)
    - Title: German (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0248)
    - Title: BT Weird / Mex Squeze (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0249)
    - Title: ZOAR: Brief (B: L. Lunch) (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0250)
    - Title: Fast quirk (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0251)
    - Title: Hawaii / L. Smooth (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0252)
    - Title: Italio (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0253)
    - Title: Drum Down / Sop Hi 18 (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0254)
    - Title: Plymouth: Build (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0255)
      Tape Brand: Sony C-60 HF
    - Title: Synco Bt (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0256)
    - Title: Gersh / T chord 1 (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0257)
    - Title: Tuba Scale (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0258)
    - Title: Dub 7 / L cut (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0259)
    - Title: Organ / Whine (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.026)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type I Position (Normal Bias) LNX
    - Title: Whip (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0261)
    - Title: This Is It / Slo Bees (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0262)
    - Title: Risk (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0263)
    - Title: Tonite / Org Scale (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0264)
    - Title: Mesian full (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0265)
    - Title: Cuba (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0266)
    - Title: Vocal Sktc (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0267)
    - Title: Mex Jig (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0268)
    - Title: Vocal whine (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0269)
    - Title: Pip Squeek (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0270)
    - Title: Sop X / Break S. (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0271)
    - Title: Ralston (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0272)
      Tape Brand: Sony Type II (CrO2) Position High Bias UX
    - Title: Ha Ha / Heaven Sent (Box 1D, Folder ID: 152.0273)
    - Title: Indian / Fire (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0274)
    - Title: Haha / Big Band (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0275)
    - Title: Blare Bt (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0276)
    - Title: Thump / Pleas (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0277)
      Tape Brand: TDK IEC II / Type II High Position
    - Title: Weill (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0278)
    - Title: Burble (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0279)
    - Title: Welsh / Bagpipe (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0280)
    - Title: Jealousy A-B (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0281)
    - Title: Trumpet (B: Ravish) (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0282)
    - Title: Indra Loop (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0283)
    - Title: Vamp Jz / Org. Carousel (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0284)
    - Title: Schuman (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0285)
    - Title: T cool (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0286)
    - Title: Yid - Horns (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0287)
    - Title: P. Sop Flick (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0288)
    - Title: Rock Funk (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0289)
    - Title: Gabble / checko (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0290)
      Tape Brand: Sony IEC I / Type I Normal Position D60
    - Title: Burp Horn (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0291)
      Tape Brand: Scotch AVC
    - Title: Bleat / Mystry (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0292)
    - Title: Baseball / Bambo (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0293)
    - Title: Hoe 2 / Veronica (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0294)
    - Title: Fiddle Squek (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0295)
    - Title: Africa (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0296)
    - Title: Jealousy (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0297)
    - Title: [Drumly] / Please (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0298)
      Tape Brand: TDK IEC II / Type II High Position SD
    - Title: Sweet (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0299)
    - Title: Piano hip (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0300)
    - Title: Orc. Shift (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0301)
    - Title: Piano / Lament (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0302)
    - Title: Slo Bongo (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0303)
    - Title: Golem # 71 (A: The Real # 71) (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0304)
    - Title: Uncon / Dub 88 (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0305)
    - Title: Jocky (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0306)
    - Title: Wish I Girl / Vocal Yearn (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0307)
    - Title: Mex / Wistful (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0308)
    - Title: How Much / Hurt (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0309)
    - Title: Chemist / Jazz Trpt (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0310)
    - Title: Strum Slo (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0311)
    - Title: Jazz Trum (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0312)
    - Title: Pres / Frantic (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0313)
      Tape Brand: TDK AV-D
    - Title: Bark / Xylo (Box 1D.a, Folder ID: 152.0314)
    - Title: Big Ben (A: Shake Wop) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0315)
    - Title: Egypt / Mystic (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0316)
    - Title: Indywhine (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0317)
    - Title: Cramps 2 (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0318)
    - Title: Can-Can / Presure (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0319)
    - Title: Busy (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0320)
    - Title: Brisk (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0321)
    - Title: Massanet / Chorus (A: Blue Steele) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0322)
    - Title: Mood (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0323)
    - Title: Bain Douch (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0324)
    - Title: Org. gone (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0325)
    - Title: Tired (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0326)
    - Title: Working / Train (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0327)
    - Title: Piano wheeze (A: John Doodle) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0328)
    - Title: Bla Synco / Epoch (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0329)
    - Title: Sex E / Twang (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0330)
    - Title: Accordian Osil (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0331)
    - Title: Whistle (A: Bell / Sleep train) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0332)
    - Title: Umpah (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0333)
    - Title: China (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0334)
    - Title: Heave Ho (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0335)
    - Title: Org Fall (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0336)
      Tape Brand: Maxell MX
    - Title: Sandslp (B: Trill / Hi Ho) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0337)
    - Title: Chair Ecst. (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0338)
    - Title: M. Org / Mon E (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0339)
    - Title: Hawaii / Crackle (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0340)
    - Title: Slow Tds (M) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0341)
    - Title: Violin Jig (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0342)
    - Title: Up-down (L) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0343)
    - Title: Violin Grave (Slo) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0344)
    - Title: Amore: primitive (A: Zither A) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0345)
    - Title: Rattle - Hit (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0346)
    - Title: Glass Breaking / Various Stones (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0347)
    - Title: Waller Swing (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0348)
    - Title: [label missing] (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0349)
    - Title: Rota Honk (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0350)
    - Title: Orch Saw (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0351)
    - Title: Fast flute (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0352)
    - Title: Scales (strings) (A: Bees) (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0353)
    - Title: Hemi-Sync Surf (Box 1E, Folder ID: 152.0354)
      Tape Brand: Hemi-Sync
    - Title: P - Wist (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0355)
    - Title: Indra Steps (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0356)
    - Title: G - up down 2 (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0357)
    - Title: Chorus / Joy P. (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0358)
    - Title: Slo Chug (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0359)
    - Title: India Beat (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0360)
    - Title: G - Saw 1 (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0361)
    - Title: Club (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0362)
    - Title: Chair Squk (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0363)
    - Title: 3 Beat (M) (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0364)
    - Title: E: steps (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0365)
    - Title: Voice / Tico (Filter) (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0366)
    - Title: G Hunt (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0367)
    - Title: Wheze Thumper (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0368)
    - Title: Irish Full (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0369)
    - Title: Tiger (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0370)
    - Title: Viol. Squek (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0371)
    - Title: Drive Car / Wawa (B: Stock Giant) (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0372)
    - Title: Indra Fiddle (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0373)
    - Title: Indra Wist (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0374)
    - Title: India foxtrot / 2nd half: Rhythm (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0375)
    - Title: 101 / Peyote Roadkill - Excerpts by William Harper (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0376)
    - Title: Honk (M) (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0377)
    - Title: Flam C (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0378)
    - Title: L. Baroom (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0379)
    - Title: Short Rota Run (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0380)
    - Title: Cord (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0381)
    - Title: Hicks / Sharpy (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0382)
    - Title: Horn Slap (B: Soft Witch) (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0383)
    - Title: Flute Slo (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0384)
    - Title: V Check / Clarinet (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0385)
      Tape Brand: Maxell XLII
    - Title: Calopie (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0386)
    - Title: Jungle Sqwak (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0387)
    - Title: Chopst / China (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0388)
    - Title: JazJig / Rose (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0389)
    - Title: Drumly (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0390)
    - Title: Zip (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0391)
    - Title: Lalo: Rose (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0392)
    - Title: Sad Slap / Stk Intro (Box 1E.a, Folder ID: 152.0393)
    - Title: Egyptology: Closing Matinee / Brazil Hoe 1 Dupe (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0394)
      Performance: Egyptology
      Related ID's: 152.0395
      Related Titles: Egyptology 5/5/83
      Tape Brand: Maxell LN
    - Title: Egyptology 5/5/83 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0395)
      Date of performance: 5/5/1983
      Related ID's: 152.0394
      Related Titles: Egyptology: Closing Matinee / Brazil Hoe 1 Dupe
    - Title: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0396)
      Performance: What Did He See
      Related ID's: 152.0397-152.0402
      Related Titles: What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway / What did he see
    - Title: What Did He See - First 13 min. only (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0397)
      Related ID's: 152.0396; 152.0398-152.0402
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway / What did he see
    - Title: (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0398)
      Related ID's: 152.0396-152.0397; 152.0399-152.0402
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway / What did he see
    - Title: (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0399)
      Related ID's: 152.0396-152.0398; 152.0400-152.0402
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway / What did he see
    - Title: (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0400)
      Related ID's: 152.0396-152.0399; 152.0401-152.0402
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway / What did he see
    - Title: What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0401)
      Related ID's: 152.0396-152.0400; 152.0402
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What did he see
    - Title: What did he see (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0402)
      Related ID's: 152.0396-152.0401
      Related Titles: (A: WDHS 6) (B: WDHS 8) / What Did He See - First 13 min. only / (A: WDHS 5) (B: WDHS 7) / (A: WDHS 2) (B: WDHS 4) / (A: WDHS 1) (B: WDHS 3) / What Did He See - [Excert?] Midway
    - Title: [Untitled] (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0403)
      Performance: I've Got The Shakes
      Related ID's: 152.0404-152.0409
      Related Titles: Shakes: Reh / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: Shakes: Reh (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0404)
      Related ID's: 152.0403; 152.0405-152.0409
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0405)
      Date of performance: 1/13/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0403-152.0404; 152.0406-152.0409
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Shakes: Reh / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0406)
      Date of performance: 4/7/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0403-152.0405; 152.0407-152.0409
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Shakes: Reh / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0407)
      Date of performance: 4/8/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0403-152.0406; 152.0409-152.0409
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Shakes: Reh / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0408)
      Date of performance: 4/6/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0403-152.0407; 152.0409
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Shakes: Reh / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes April 2, 1995 Sunday (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0409)
      Date of performance: 4/2/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0403-152.0408
      Related Titles: [Untitled] / Shakes: Reh / Jan 13, 1995 - I've Got The Shakes - Richard Foreman / I've Got The Shakes April 7, 1995 Friday / I've Got The Shakes Saturday April 8, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes Thursday April 6, 1995
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes Tuesday April 4, 1995 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0410)
      Date of performance: 4/4/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0411-152.0413
      Related Titles: I've Got The Shakes March 30, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 1, 1995 Saturday / I've Got The Shakes March 31, 1995 Friday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes March 30, 1995 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0411)
      Date of performance: 3/30/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0410; 152.0412-152.0413
      Related Titles: I've Got The Shakes Tuesday April 4, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 1, 1995 Saturday / I've Got The Shakes March 31, 1995 Friday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes April 1, 1995 Saturday (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0412)
      Date of performance: 4/1/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0410-152.0411; 152.0413
      Related Titles: I've Got The Shakes Tuesday April 4, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes March 30, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes March 31, 1995 Friday
    - Title: I've Got The Shakes March 31, 1995 Friday (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0413)
      Date of performance: 3/31/1995
      Related ID's: 152.0410-152.0412
      Related Titles: I've Got The Shakes Tuesday April 4, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes March 30, 1995 / I've Got The Shakes April 1, 1995 Saturday
    - Title: Eddie 4/10 - 1/2 only (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0414)
      Date of performance: 10-Apr
      Related ID's: 152.0415-152.0419
      Related Titles: Eddie - Voice Tape - New City '90 / Eddie NY 4/12 / Eddie RF / Eddie (RF) NY / Low Eddie
    - Title: Eddie - Voice Tape - New City '90 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0415)
      Related ID's: 152.0414; 152.0416-152.0419
      Related Titles: Eddie 4/10 - 1/2 only / Eddie NY 4/12 / Eddie RF / Eddie (RF) NY / Low Eddie
      Tape Brand: Sony UX-S
    - Title: Eddie NY 4/12 (Box 1F, Folder ID: 152.0416)
      Related ID's: 152.0414-152.0415; 152.0417-152.0419